{"id": "2646105921bf1c2515179b081481505a", "table_id": "1029", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "5911", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "in 2013/2014, on an average day, there were 11,493 adults in remand in the 12 reporting provinces and territories.", "question": "in 2013/2014, on an average day, how many adults in the 12 reporting provinces and territories are in remand?", "answer": [11493.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"adults in remand": {"(0, 4)": "remand"}}, "left": {"in the 12 reporting provinces and territories": {"(14, 0)": "provinces and territories - total"}, "12": {"(2, 0)": "newfoundland and labrador", "(3, 0)": "prince edward island", "(4, 0)": "nova scotia", "(5, 0)": "new brunswick", "(6, 0)": "quebec", "(7, 0)": "ontario", "(8, 0)": "manitoba", "(9, 0)": "saskatchewan", "(10, 0)": "british columbia", "(11, 0)": "yukon", "(12, 0)": "northwest territories", "(13, 0)": "nunavut"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(14, 4)": 11493.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=E17"], "reference_cells_map": {"E17": "(14, 4)"}}
{"id": "518d25285dcc848a543e07ae03103ab1", "table_id": "1029", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "5911", "sub_sentence_id": "2", "sub_sentence": "in 2013/2014, on an average day, there were 9,889 adults in sentenced custody in the 12 reporting provinces and territories.", "question": "in 2013/2014, on an average day, how many adults are in sentenced custody in the 12 reporting provinces and territories?", "answer": [9889.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"adults in sentenced custody": {"(0, 1)": "sentenced custody"}}, "left": {"in the 12 reporting provinces and territories": {"(14, 0)": "provinces and territories - total"}, "12": {"(2, 0)": "newfoundland and labrador", "(3, 0)": "prince edward island", "(4, 0)": "nova scotia", "(5, 0)": "new brunswick", "(6, 0)": "quebec", "(7, 0)": "ontario", "(8, 0)": "manitoba", "(9, 0)": "saskatchewan", "(10, 0)": "british columbia", "(11, 0)": "yukon", "(12, 0)": "northwest territories", "(13, 0)": "nunavut"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(14, 1)": 9889.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=B17"], "reference_cells_map": {"B17": "(14, 1)"}}
{"id": "51a9278d6eeb26d8a864ad7b1e0f3df9", "table_id": "1029", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "5912", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "on average, there were 84,905 adult offenders on probation on any given day in 2013/2014 in the 12 reporting provinces and territories.", "question": "on average, how many adult offenders are on probation on any given day in 2013/2014 in the 12 reporting provinces and territories?", "answer": [84905.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"adult offenders on probation": {"(0, 7)": "probation"}}, "left": {"in the 12 reporting provinces and territories": {"(14, 0)": "provinces and territories - total"}, "12": {"(2, 0)": "newfoundland and labrador", "(3, 0)": "prince edward island", "(4, 0)": "nova scotia", "(5, 0)": "new brunswick", "(6, 0)": "quebec", "(7, 0)": "ontario", "(8, 0)": "manitoba", "(9, 0)": "saskatchewan", "(10, 0)": "british columbia", "(11, 0)": "yukon", "(12, 0)": "northwest territories", "(13, 0)": "nunavut"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(14, 7)": 84905.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=H17"], "reference_cells_map": {"H17": "(14, 7)"}}
{"id": "6e70535d7c12f08c20dd6e6885b3c5d8", "table_id": "1306", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "7333", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "homeowners with or without a mortgage were significantly less likely to have used a payday loan, compared with non-owners.", "question": "which kind of home ownership status was most likely to have used a payday loan, homeowners with or without a mortgage, or non-owners?", "answer": ["do not own"], "aggregation": ["argmax"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"use a payday loan": {"(0, 3)": "payday loan used in past three years"}}, "left": {"homeowners with a mortgage": {"(40, 0)": "own with mortgage"}, "homeowners without a mortgage": {"(39, 0)": "own without mortgage"}, "non-owners": {"(41, 0)": "do not own"}, "[ANSWER]": {"(41, 0)": "do not own"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {}}, "answer_formulas": ["=A44"], "reference_cells_map": {"A44": "(41, 0)"}}
{"id": "2032392561898891afecccf6c6b4d4f8", "table_id": "1306", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "7334", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "a higher level of education was associated with a lower probability of payday loan use. those with a university degree had the lowest probability of payday loan use.", "question": "which level of education had the lowest probability of payday loan use?", "answer": ["university diploma or degree"], "aggregation": ["argmin"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"probability of payday loan use": {"(0, 3)": "payday loan used in past three years"}}, "left": {"level of education": {"(18, 0)": "education of main income earner"}, "[ANSWER]": {"(22, 0)": "university diploma or degree"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {}}, "answer_formulas": ["=A25"], "reference_cells_map": {"A25": "(22, 0)"}}
{"id": "dda5ce4fa44caa2c3db63ccf56a4bc55", "table_id": "1306", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "7336", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "lone-parent families and \"other\" family types were more likely to use payday loans, compared with couples with no children.", "question": "which family type was least likely to use payday loans, among lone-parent families, \"other\" family typs and couples with no children?", "answer": ["couple with no children"], "aggregation": ["argmin"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"use payday loans": {"(0, 3)": "payday loan used in past three years"}}, "left": {"lone-parent families": {"(16, 0)": "lone parent"}, "\"other\"family types": {"(17, 0)": "\"other\" family types"}, "couples with no children": {"(14, 0)": "couple with no children"}, "[ANSWER]": {"(14, 0)": "couple with no children"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {}}, "answer_formulas": ["=A17"], "reference_cells_map": {"A17": "(14, 0)"}}
{"id": "4cbf4092cb6a66e3e62a9f0312a57d00", "table_id": "1306", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "7337", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "quebec residents were least likely to use payday loans among residents of all the regions.", "question": "which region was the least likely to use payday loans among all the regions?", "answer": ["quebec"], "aggregation": ["argmin"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"use payday loans": {"(0, 3)": "payday loan used in past three years"}}, "left": {"all the regions": {"(29, 0)": "region"}, "[ANSWER]": {"(31, 0)": "quebec"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {}}, "answer_formulas": ["=A34"], "reference_cells_map": {"A34": "(31, 0)"}}
{"id": "2802b5a96c112c97d86cf16d30653006", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8585", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "48.2% of imports in capital goods originated from the united states in 2016.", "question": "how many percentage points of imports in capital goods were originated from the united states in 2016?", "answer": [48.2], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in 2016": {"(0, 6)": "share in 2016"}}, "left": {"imports in capital goods": {"(2, 0)": "imports of capital goods"}, "the united states": {"(4, 0)": "united states"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(4, 6)": 48.2}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=G7"], "reference_cells_map": {"G7": "(4, 6)"}}
{"id": "bf3958b89b05b7c9a641d0c55212d2f3", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8585", "sub_sentence_id": "2", "sub_sentence": "19% of imports in capital goods originated from china in 2016.", "question": "how many percentage points of imports in capital goods were originated from china in 2016?", "answer": [19.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in 2016": {"(0, 6)": "share in 2016"}}, "left": {"imports in capital goods": {"(2, 0)": "imports of capital goods"}, "china": {"(5, 0)": "china"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(5, 6)": 19.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=G8"], "reference_cells_map": {"G8": "(5, 6)"}}
{"id": "1b2c4ef824ff07feb381ca7083a325b7", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8585", "sub_sentence_id": "3", "sub_sentence": "8.8% of imports in capital goods originated from mexico in 2016.", "question": "how many percentage points of imports in capital goods were originated from mexico in 2016?", "answer": [8.8], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in 2016": {"(0, 6)": "share in 2016"}}, "left": {"imports in capital goods": {"(2, 0)": "imports of capital goods"}, "mexico": {"(6, 0)": "mexico"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(6, 6)": 8.8}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=G9"], "reference_cells_map": {"G9": "(6, 6)"}}
{"id": "ce58778079e7e8296b7dfeab88a97358", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8585", "sub_sentence_id": "4", "sub_sentence": "3.9% of imports in capital goods originated from south korea in 2016.", "question": "how many percentage points of imports in capital goods were originated from south korea in 2016?", "answer": [3.9], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in 2016": {"(0, 6)": "share in 2016"}}, "left": {"imports in capital goods": {"(2, 0)": "imports of capital goods"}, "south korea": {"(7, 0)": "south korea"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(7, 6)": 3.9}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=G10"], "reference_cells_map": {"G10": "(7, 6)"}}
{"id": "7c1faea02da50e0d14a0e7516a158e31", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8585", "sub_sentence_id": "5", "sub_sentence": "3.6% of imports in capital goods originated from germany.", "question": "how many percentage points of imports in capital goods were originated from germany in 2016?", "answer": [3.6], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in 2016": {"(0, 6)": "share in 2016"}}, "left": {"imports in capital goods": {"(2, 0)": "imports of capital goods"}, "germany": {"(8, 0)": "germany"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(8, 6)": 3.6}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=G11"], "reference_cells_map": {"G11": "(8, 6)"}}
{"id": "0eef65c4adb1e41d82b4cf329f142ca9", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8587", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "also to note, while capital goods imports from vietnam reached $1.6 billion in 2016.", "question": "how many capital goods imports from vietnam in 2016?", "answer": [1.6], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in 2016": {"(0, 4)": 2016.0}}, "left": {"capital goods imports": {"(2, 0)": "imports of capital goods"}, "vietnam": {"(10, 0)": "vietnam"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(10, 4)": 1.6}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=E13"], "reference_cells_map": {"E13": "(10, 4)"}}
{"id": "7383721bf1f78a4e05a8a7bfe90f252e", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8588", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "in 2016, 72.5% of capital goods exports were destined for the united states.", "question": "in 2016, how many percentage points of capital goods exports were destined for the united states?", "answer": [72.5], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in 2016": {"(0, 6)": "share in 2016"}}, "left": {"capital goods exports": {"(14, 0)": "exports of capital goods"}, "the united states": {"(16, 0)": "united states"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(16, 6)": 72.5}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=G19"], "reference_cells_map": {"G19": "(16, 6)"}}
{"id": "03f011d22eead3ec50f226879b47f531", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8588", "sub_sentence_id": "2", "sub_sentence": "in 2016, 2.9% of capital goods exports were destined for china.", "question": "in 2016, how many percentage points of capital goods exports were destined for china?", "answer": [2.9], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in 2016": {"(0, 6)": "share in 2016"}}, "left": {"capital goods exports": {"(14, 0)": "exports of capital goods"}, "china": {"(17, 0)": "china"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(17, 6)": 2.9}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=G20"], "reference_cells_map": {"G20": "(17, 6)"}}
{"id": "f065d4b7b2d2ac593561555d347d5ae4", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8588", "sub_sentence_id": "3", "sub_sentence": "in 2016, 2.5% of capital goods exports were destined for the united kingdom.", "question": "in 2016, how many percentage points of capital goods exports were destined for the united kingdom?", "answer": [2.5], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in 2016": {"(0, 6)": "share in 2016"}}, "left": {"capital goods exports": {"(14, 0)": "exports of capital goods"}, "united kingdom": {"(18, 0)": "united kingdom"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(18, 6)": 2.5}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=G21"], "reference_cells_map": {"G21": "(18, 6)"}}
{"id": "9594884276d0eba1d4097c5f179fc5fd", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8589", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "malta was the fourth-largest destination of capital goods exports in 2016.", "question": "which place was the fourth-largest destination of capital goods exports in 2016?", "answer": ["malta"], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in 2016": {"(0, 4)": 2016.0}}, "left": {"capital goods exports": {"(14, 0)": "exports of capital goods"}, "[ANSWER]": {"(19, 0)": "malta"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {}}, "answer_formulas": ["=A22"], "reference_cells_map": {"A22": "(19, 0)"}}
{"id": "460624dde30218e9471b8a3c8e49142f", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8590", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "exports to the united states were the largest contributor to the decrease of capital goods exports as they declined on average by 2.8% over the period 2000 to 2016.", "question": "over the period 2000 to 2016, how many percentage points of capital goods exports to the united states has declined?", "answer": [2.8], "aggregation": ["opposite"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"2000 to 2016": {"(0, 7)": "growth rate 2000 to 2016"}}, "left": {"capital goods exports": {"(14, 0)": "exports of capital goods"}, "the united states": {"(16, 0)": "united states"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(16, 7)": -2.8}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=-H19"], "reference_cells_map": {"H19": "(16, 7)"}}
{"id": "02f85b626425f7c9a17b4e6132f7c6c5", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8591", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "exports to the united kingdom contracted slightly, by 0.5% over the period 2000 to 2016.", "question": "over the period 2000 to 2016, how many percentage points of capital goods exports to the united kingdom has declined?", "answer": [0.5], "aggregation": ["opposite"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"2000 to 2016": {"(0, 7)": "growth rate 2000 to 2016"}}, "left": {"capital goods exports": {"(14, 0)": "exports of capital goods"}, "the united kingdom": {"(18, 0)": "united kingdom"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(18, 7)": -0.5}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=-H21"], "reference_cells_map": {"H21": "(18, 7)"}}
{"id": "cbee385ab375aea58f15533afcb9f016", "table_id": "1539", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "8591", "sub_sentence_id": "2", "sub_sentence": "exports to germany contracted slightly, by 0.1% over the period 2000 to 2016.", "question": "over the period 2000 to 2016, how many percentage points of capital goods exports to germany has declined?", "answer": [0.1], "aggregation": ["opposite"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"2000 to 2016": {"(0, 7)": "growth rate 2000 to 2016"}}, "left": {"capital goods exports": {"(14, 0)": "exports of capital goods"}, "germany": {"(20, 0)": "germany"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(20, 7)": -0.1}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=-H23"], "reference_cells_map": {"H23": "(20, 7)"}}
{"id": "c3e0a3d0e22b8dec298886bd87a9ee4c", "table_id": "1623", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "9189", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "senior women living in couples were more likely than senior women living alone to report having a large number of close family members.", "question": "which is more likely to report having a large number (5 or more) of close family members ,senior women living in couples or senior women living alone.", "answer": ["living in a couple"], "aggregation": ["pair-argmax"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"[ANSWER]": {"(1, 2)": "living in a couple"}}, "left": {"having a large number (5 or more) of close family members": {"(6, 0)": "five or more"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"senior women living in couples": {"(6, 2)": 58.0}, "senior women living alone": {"(6, 1)": 46.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C4"], "reference_cells_map": {"C4": "(1, 2)"}}
{"id": "56a8475c602ebb357098e1fd778f18c8", "table_id": "1623", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "9190", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "senior women living in couples were more likely to report having a large number of acquaintances, compared with their counterparts living alone.", "question": "which is more likely to report having a large number of acquaintances,senior women living in couples or senior women living alone.", "answer": ["living in a couple"], "aggregation": ["pair-argmax"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"[ANSWER]": {"(1, 2)": "living in a couple"}}, "left": {"having a large number of acquaintances": {"(14, 0)": "five or more"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"senior women living in couples": {"(14, 2)": 78.0}, "senior women living alone": {"(14, 1)": 72.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C4"], "reference_cells_map": {"C4": "(1, 2)"}}
{"id": "0c7ab784c63870ac19690998aef3434d", "table_id": "1623", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "9193", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "senior men living in couples were more likely than those living alone to report having a large number of close friends.", "question": "which is more likely to report having a large number of close friends,senior men living in couples or senior men living alone.", "answer": ["living in a couple"], "aggregation": ["pair-argmax"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"[ANSWER]": {"(1, 4)": "living in a couple"}}, "left": {"having a large number of close friends": {"(10, 0)": "five or more"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"senior men living in couples": {"(10, 4)": 45.0}, "senior men living alone": {"(10, 3)": 36.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=E4"], "reference_cells_map": {"E4": "(1, 4)"}}
{"id": "7158874351376b2d503fb1764f50bba0", "table_id": "16_totto2005-0", "table_source": "totto", "sentence_id": "0", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "chris allen started his career with oxford united in the 1991-92 second division, where he played fourteen games.", "question": "how many games did chris allen play as he was starting his career with oxford united in the 1991-92 second division?", "answer": [14.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"games": {"(1, 3)": "apps"}}, "left": {"oxford united": {"(2, 0)": "oxford united"}, "1991-92": {"(2, 1)": "1991-92"}, "second division": {"(2, 2)": "second division"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(2, 3)": 14.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=D5"], "reference_cells_map": {"D5": "(2, 3)"}}
{"id": "73512fe9ca199714fb81c28e5e4f8d45", "table_id": "200_totto23645-4", "table_source": "totto", "sentence_id": "0", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "andrew williams is a footballer and played 278 league games in an eleven-year career in the football league.", "question": "how many league games did andrew williams (born 1962) play in his career?", "answer": [278.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"league games": {"(1, 3)": "apps"}}, "left": {"eleven-year career": {"(25, 0)": "career total"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(25, 3)": 278.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=D28"], "reference_cells_map": {"D28": "(25, 3)"}}
{"id": "ff4a04c8eaf1d881f6c6795fb320978a", "table_id": "2040", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "11380", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "the inter-industry component is larger than the own-industry component for agriculture, forestry, fishing and hunting sector.", "question": "which component of structural adjustment is larger for agriculture, forestry, fishing and hunting sector? the inter-industry component or the own-industry component?", "answer": ["inter-industry"], "aggregation": ["pair-argmax"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"own-industry": {"(0, 1)": "own-industry"}, "[ANSWER]": {"(0, 4)": "inter-industry"}}, "left": {"agriculture, forestry, fishing and hunting sector": {"(5, 0)": "agriculture, forestry, fishing and hunting"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {}}, "answer_formulas": ["=E3"], "reference_cells_map": {"E3": "(0, 4)"}}
{"id": "884d26e2e1b2840d8220f815883715e1", "table_id": "2040", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "11381", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "mining, oil and gas had the largest positive own-industry structural adjustment in the 2000s.", "question": "which industry had the largest positive own-industry structural adjustment in the 2000s?", "answer": ["mining and oil and gas extraction"], "aggregation": ["argmax"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in the 2000s": {"(1, 2)": "2000s"}, "own-industry structural adjustment": {"(0, 1)": "own-industry"}}, "left": {"[ANSWER]": {"(6, 0)": "mining and oil and gas extraction"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {}}, "answer_formulas": ["=A9"], "reference_cells_map": {"A9": "(6, 0)"}}
{"id": "8dd51c0d167bb4799862b34d39659ddb", "table_id": "2040", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "11382", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "mining, oil and gas resulted in inter-industry effect of -0.06 percentage points in 2000s.", "question": "what is the inter-industry effect of mining, oil and gas sector in 2000s?", "answer": [-0.06], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"inter-industry": {"(0, 4)": "inter-industry"}, "2000s": {"(1, 5)": "2000s"}}, "left": {"mining, oil and gas": {"(6, 0)": "mining and oil and gas extraction"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(6, 5)": -0.06}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=F9"], "reference_cells_map": {"F9": "(6, 5)"}}
{"id": "69bdfd0e145ac8cd99ee3a5d3b13fe73", "table_id": "2040", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "11383", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "total structural effect is 0.31 percentage points for mining and oil and gas extraction sector in 2000s.", "question": "what is the total structural effect for mining and oil and gas extraction sector in 2000s?", "answer": [0.32], "aggregation": ["sum"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"total structural effect": {"(0, 1)": "own-industry"}, "2000s": {"(1, 5)": "2000s"}}, "left": {"mining and oil and gas extraction": {"(6, 0)": "mining and oil and gas extraction"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(6, 2)": 0.38, "(6, 5)": -0.06}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C9+F9"], "reference_cells_map": {"C9": "(6, 2)", "F9": "(6, 5)"}}
{"id": "36d8d33adbbde40c928a18ad58617c96", "table_id": "2040", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "11384", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "finance, insurance and real estate had 0.10 percentage point own-industry structural impact in 2000s.", "question": "what is the own-industry structural impact on finance, insurance and real estate sector in 2000s.", "answer": [0.1], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"2000s": {"(1, 2)": "2000s"}, "own-industry": {"(0, 1)": "own-industry"}}, "left": {"finance, insurance and real estate": {"(14, 0)": "finance, insurance, real estate and renting and leasing"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(14, 2)": 0.1}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C17"], "reference_cells_map": {"C17": "(14, 2)"}}
{"id": "43c6eec15be7b03ce9dd0ce0c14830ab", "table_id": "2040", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "11385", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "finance, insurance and real estate had 0.04 percentage point total structural impact in 2000s.", "question": "what is the total structural impact on finance, insurance and real estate sector in 2000s?", "answer": [0.04], "aggregation": ["sum"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"2000s": {"(1, 5)": "2000s"}, "total structural impact": {"(0, 1)": "own-industry"}}, "left": {"finance, insurance and real estate": {"(14, 0)": "finance, insurance, real estate and renting and leasing"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(14, 2)": 0.1, "(14, 5)": -0.06}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C17+F17"], "reference_cells_map": {"C17": "(14, 2)", "F17": "(14, 5)"}}
{"id": "bb18741822a78fdacb1104536371c7cd", "table_id": "2040", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "11386", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "construction's own-industry term was 0.25 percentage points in 2000s.", "question": "what is the construction's own-industry term in 2000s?", "answer": [0.25], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"2000s": {"(1, 2)": "2000s"}, "own-industry": {"(0, 1)": "own-industry"}}, "left": {"construction": {"(8, 0)": "construction"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(8, 2)": 0.25}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C11"], "reference_cells_map": {"C11": "(8, 2)"}}
{"id": "2c3fd2e3c8104127c65b6af4243e16c2", "table_id": "2040", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "11386", "sub_sentence_id": "2", "sub_sentence": "construction's inter-industry term was -0.30 percentage points in 2000s.", "question": "what is the construction's inter-industry term in 2000s.", "answer": [-0.3], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"2000s": {"(1, 5)": "2000s"}, "inter-industry term": {"(0, 4)": "inter-industry"}}, "left": {"construction": {"(8, 0)": "construction"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(8, 5)": -0.3}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=F11"], "reference_cells_map": {"F11": "(8, 5)"}}
{"id": "cd89b24197384159eb1b3f8a829b1319", "table_id": "2040", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "11387", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "construction's total structural adjustment is -0.06 percentage points in 2000s.", "question": "what is the construction's total structural adjustment in 2000s.", "answer": [-0.05], "aggregation": ["sum"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"2000s": {"(1, 2)": "2000s"}, "total structural adjustment": {"(0, 1)": "own-industry"}}, "left": {"construction": {"(8, 0)": "construction"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(8, 2)": 0.25, "(8, 5)": -0.3}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C11+F11"], "reference_cells_map": {"C11": "(8, 2)", "F11": "(8, 5)"}}
{"id": "21ff79c88b1d7136ec5b9955384c679d", "table_id": "2354", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "12655", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "during the 2000s the chronic low-income rate among all immigrants peaked at 16.3% in 2004 and declined to 12.3% by 2012.", "question": "during the 2000s the chronic low-income rate,what was the maximum in 2014 and 2012 respectively?", "answer": [16.3, 12.3], "aggregation": ["max"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {}, "left": {"2004": {"(8, 0)": 2004.0}, "2012": {"(30, 0)": 2012.0}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(8, 4)": 16.3, "(16, 4)": 12.3}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=E11", "=E19"], "reference_cells_map": {"E11": "(8, 4)", "E19": "(16, 4)"}}
{"id": "3aaa1d7c65cdea308415e75640664494", "table_id": "2354", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "12656", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "the 22% decline in chronic low income among immigrants between 2000 and 2012 was less than that observed among the comparison group (mainly the canadian-born), which fell by 39%, from 6.1% to 3.7% over the period.", "question": "what were the rates of observed among the comparison group in 2000 and 2012 respectively?", "answer": [6.1, 3.7], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"comparison group": {"(1, 5)": "comparison group"}}, "left": {"2000": {"(4, 0)": 2000.0}, "2012": {"(16, 0)": 2012.0}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(4, 5)": 6.1, "(16, 5)": 3.7}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=F7", "=F19"], "reference_cells_map": {"F7": "(4, 5)", "F19": "(16, 5)"}}
{"id": "af66f83e0d436cdd09dad110e5fd232d", "table_id": "2354", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "12657", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "in 2012, however, there was little difference in the chronic low-income rates between those in canada for 5 to 10 years and 16 to 20 years.", "question": "in 2012,what were the rates of chronic low-income in canada for 5 to 10 years and 16 to 20 years respectively?", "answer": [13.3, 11.5], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"5 to 10 years": {"(1, 1)": "5 to 10 years"}, "16 to 20 years": {"(1, 3)": "16 to 20 years"}}, "left": {"canada": {"(3, 0)": "overall"}, "2012": {"(16, 0)": 2012.0}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(16, 1)": 13.3, "(16, 3)": 11.5}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=B19", "=D19"], "reference_cells_map": {"B19": "(16, 1)", "D19": "(16, 3)"}}
{"id": "372596718b1e2b5e944560f67bd68bb7", "table_id": "2552", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "13672", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "26% of donors considered a government tax credit to be an important reason.", "question": "how many percentage points did donors consider a government tax credit to be an important reason?", "answer": [26.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"donors": {"(1, 1)": "all donors"}}, "left": {"reason": {"(3, 0)": "reasons for donating"}, "government tax credit": {"(5, 0)": "the government will give you a credit on your income taxes"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(5, 1)": 26.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=B8"], "reference_cells_map": {"B8": "(5, 1)"}}
{"id": "6df2b397f92c084e94b123bda3430b24", "table_id": "2552", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "13675", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "72% of women reported that they or someone they knew had been personally affected by the cause the organization supports.", "question": "how many percentage points did women report that they or someone they knew had been personally affected by the cause the organization supports?", "answer": [72.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"women": {"(1, 5)": "women"}}, "left": {"had been personally affected by the cause the organization supports": {"(4, 0)": "you or someone you know has been personally affected by the cause the organization supports"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(4, 5)": 72.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=F7"], "reference_cells_map": {"F7": "(4, 5)"}}
{"id": "c4a0e51eabe0ba94c9178bd53726ddc5", "table_id": "2552", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "13675", "sub_sentence_id": "2", "sub_sentence": "63% of men reported that they or someone they knew had been personally affected by the cause the organization supports.", "question": "how many percentage points did men report that they or someone they knew had been personally affected by the cause the organization supports?", "answer": [63.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"men": {"(1, 4)": "men"}}, "left": {"had been personally affected by the cause the organization supports": {"(4, 0)": "you or someone you know has been personally affected by the cause the organization supports"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(4, 4)": 63.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=E7"], "reference_cells_map": {"E7": "(4, 4)"}}
{"id": "67f392f7284fa56c26e23005392c0e8d", "table_id": "2552", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "13677", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "52% of donors in the 35-to-54 age group reported that they made a donation because a family member or acquaintance had asked them to.", "question": "how many percentage points did donors in the 35-to-54 age group report that they made a donation because a family member or acquaintance had asked them to?", "answer": [52.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"in the 35-to-54 age group": {"(1, 7)": "35 to 54 years"}}, "left": {"a family member or acquaintance had asked them to": {"(10, 0)": "a family member, friend, neighbour or colleague requested that you make a donation"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(10, 7)": 52.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=H13"], "reference_cells_map": {"H13": "(10, 7)"}}
{"id": "4fde11ce6aaf029cca45f4c7fb67b75e", "table_id": "2552", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "13678", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "this proportion of donors reporting that they made a donation because a family member or acquaintance had asked them to was 39% for donors 55 years and older.", "question": "how many percentage points did donors in the 55 years and older age group report that they made a donation because a family member or acquaintance had asked them to?", "answer": [39.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"55 years and older": {"(1, 8)": "55 years and older"}}, "left": {"a family member or acquaintance had asked them to": {"(10, 0)": "a family member, friend, neighbour or colleague requested that you make a donation"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(10, 8)": 39.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=I13"], "reference_cells_map": {"I13": "(10, 8)"}}
{"id": "ded239819a69ddef48a9b65ff00b02fa", "table_id": "2558", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "13723", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "reduced border costs lead to an 82% increase in exports from canada to the united states.", "question": "how many percentage points of increase in exports from canada to the united states do rudeuced border costs lead?", "answer": [82.2], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"exports from canada to the united states": {"(1, 1)": "canada to the united states"}}, "left": {"reduced border costs": {"(3, 0)": "reduction in border costs"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(3, 1)": 82.2}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=B6"], "reference_cells_map": {"B6": "(3, 1)"}}
{"id": "a467f059727ad5dc8984b4559d1fbcbf", "table_id": "2558", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "13723", "sub_sentence_id": "2", "sub_sentence": "reduced border costs lead to an 82% increase in exports from canada to the united states.", "question": "how many percentage points of increase in exports from canada to the united states do rudeuced border costs lead?", "answer": [71.6], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"exports from canada to the united states": {"(1, 2)": "united states to canada"}}, "left": {"reduced border costs": {"(3, 0)": "reduction in border costs"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(3, 2)": 71.6}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C6"], "reference_cells_map": {"C6": "(3, 2)"}}
{"id": "f594dbeb26040a1b29762a22413ee4c7", "table_id": "2558", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "13724", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "inter-provincial trade falls by 52% due to reduced border costs.", "question": "how many percentage points does inter-provincial trade fall due to rudeuced border costs?", "answer": [52], "aggregation": ["opposite"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"inter-provincial trade": {"(1, 3)": "inter-provincial"}}, "left": {"reduced border costs": {"(3, 0)": "reduction in border costs"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(3, 3)": -52.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=-D6"], "reference_cells_map": {"D6": "(3, 3)"}}
{"id": "60d316baf19941a8289fb89c8eec5f74", "table_id": "2558", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "13724", "sub_sentence_id": "2", "sub_sentence": "intra-provincial trade falls by over 46% due to reduced border costs.", "question": "how many percentage points does intra-provincial trade fall due to rudeuced border costs?", "answer": [46.1], "aggregation": ["opposite"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"intra-provincial trade": {"(1, 4)": "intra-provincial"}}, "left": {"reduced border costs": {"(3, 0)": "reduction in border costs"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(3, 4)": -46.1}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=-E6"], "reference_cells_map": {"E6": "(3, 4)"}}
{"id": "49125ca8ebe9d6a1e09915a85693debd", "table_id": "2558", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "13727", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "an increase to mfn tariffs plus associated non-tariff barriers reduces canadian exports to the united states by 23%.", "question": "how many percentage points of increase does an increase to mfn tariffs plus associated non-tariff barriers reduce canadian exports to the united states?", "answer": [23.4], "aggregation": ["opposite"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"canadian exports to the united states": {"(1, 1)": "canada to the united states"}}, "left": {"increase to mfn tariffs plus associated non-tariff barriers": {"(4, 0)": "increase in border costs"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(4, 1)": -23.4}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=-B7"], "reference_cells_map": {"B7": "(4, 1)"}}
{"id": "abd0f4b5af253ad81a6a37d007473067", "table_id": "2558", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "13727", "sub_sentence_id": "2", "sub_sentence": "an increase to mfn tariffs plus associated non-tariff barriers reduces u.s. exports to canada by 18%.", "question": "how many percentage points of increase does an increase to mfn tariffs plus associated non-tariff barriers reduce u.s. exports to canada?", "answer": [18.1], "aggregation": ["opposite"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"u.s. exports to canada": {"(1, 2)": "united states to canada"}}, "left": {}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(4, 2)": -18.1}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=-C7"], "reference_cells_map": {"C7": "(4, 2)"}}
{"id": "c71737a27a08e1c4f4b634d20931f94a", "table_id": "294_totto33628-0", "table_source": "totto", "sentence_id": "0", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "in 2012, alex played with the chicago fire of major league soccer.", "question": "in 2012, which club of major league soccer did alex sign for?", "answer": ["chicago fire"], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {}, "left": {"2012": {"(6, 1)": 2012.0}, "[ANSWER]": {"(6, 0)": "chicago fire"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"major league soccer": {"(6, 2)": "major league soccer"}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=A9"], "reference_cells_map": {"A9": "(6, 0)"}}
{"id": "128d76364595d32bb724343756424f24", "table_id": "348_totto39402-0", "table_source": "totto", "sentence_id": "0", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "in the 2005-2006 season, martin made his debut in ligue 1 for as monaco.", "question": "which club did martin play for in 2005-06?", "answer": ["as monaco"], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {}, "left": {"2005-2006": {"(2, 1)": "2005-06"}, "[ANSWER]": {"(2, 0)": "as monaco"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"1": {"(2, 2)": "ligue 1"}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=A5"], "reference_cells_map": {"A5": "(2, 0)"}}
{"id": "3f4fa0ee2df42fc5b9140b58b54eb203", "table_id": "45", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "156", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "in 2016, 7.2% of all farm operations had exclusively female operators.", "question": "what percent of all farm operations is exclusively for female operators?", "answer": [7.2], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"exclusively female operators": {"(0, 2)": "female only"}}, "left": {"all farm operations": {"(7, 0)": "all farm types"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(7, 2)": 7.2}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C10"], "reference_cells_map": {"C10": "(7, 2)"}}
{"id": "8bbfc8a469b26d6b01003ed89f69a734", "table_id": "45", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "156", "sub_sentence_id": "2", "sub_sentence": "in 2016, 60.1% of all farm operations is male-only.", "question": "what percent of all farm operations is male only?", "answer": [60.1], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"male-only": {"(0, 1)": "male only"}}, "left": {"all farm operations": {"(7, 0)": "all farm types"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(7, 1)": 60.1}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=B10"], "reference_cells_map": {"B10": "(7, 1)"}}
{"id": "1e3d55c3064aaa53501641c27ed2a749", "table_id": "45", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "157", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "horse and other equine type farms were most likely to have female-only operations among all \"other livestock\" farm types.", "question": "which farms types were most likely to have female-only operations among all \"other livestock\" farm types?", "answer": ["horse and other equine"], "aggregation": ["argmax"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"female-only operations": {"(0, 2)": "female only"}}, "left": {"[ANSWER]": {"(3, 0)": "horse and other equine"}}, "top_left_corner": {"among all \"other livestock\" farm types": {"(0, 0)": "farm type"}}}, "quantity_link": {}}, "answer_formulas": ["=A6"], "reference_cells_map": {"A6": "(3, 0)"}}
{"id": "c2594da43e44e87d4aa47c5830292fac", "table_id": "45", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "158", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "19.1% of the horse and other equine type farms had female operators exclusively.", "question": "what percent of the horse and other equine type farms is female only?", "answer": [19.1], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"female operators exclusively": {"(0, 2)": "female only"}}, "left": {"horse and other equine type farms": {"(3, 0)": "horse and other equine"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(3, 2)": 19.1}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C6"], "reference_cells_map": {"C6": "(3, 2)"}}
{"id": "0df691e32f7d7ca783ba5083af7f3990", "table_id": "45", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "158", "sub_sentence_id": "2", "sub_sentence": "36.6% of the horse and other equine type farms had only male operators.", "question": "what percent of the horse and other equine type farms is male only?", "answer": [36.6], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"only male operators": {"(0, 1)": "male only"}}, "left": {"horse and other equine type farms": {"(3, 0)": "horse and other equine"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(3, 1)": 36.6}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=B6"], "reference_cells_map": {"B6": "(3, 1)"}}
{"id": "c2b81f5d14fdb3e2fdf26b9edce41a48", "table_id": "45", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "158", "sub_sentence_id": "3", "sub_sentence": "44.2% of horse and other equine type farms had both male operators and female operators.", "question": "what percent of the horse and other equine type farms had both male and female operators?", "answer": [44.2], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"both male operators and female operators": {"(0, 3)": "male and female"}}, "left": {"horse and other equine type farms": {"(3, 0)": "horse and other equine"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(3, 3)": 44.2}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=D6"], "reference_cells_map": {"D6": "(3, 3)"}}
{"id": "549e5db875507daf08c1c8f86900e3ac", "table_id": "477_totto54274-0", "table_source": "totto", "sentence_id": "0", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "in 2000, fazande rushed 368 yards on 119 carries and two touchdowns for chargers.", "question": "how many rushing yards did fazande get in 2000?", "answer": [368.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"rushing yards": {"(1, 5)": "yds"}}, "left": {"2000": {"(3, 0)": 2000.0}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"119": {"(3, 4)": 119.0}, "two": {"(3, 8)": 2.0}, "[ANSWER]": {"(3, 5)": 368.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=F6"], "reference_cells_map": {"F6": "(3, 5)"}}
{"id": "f6a44e7a26ac8f6ed0eb90f8ceb56883", "table_id": "553_totto63480-3", "table_source": "totto", "sentence_id": "0", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "the never story peaked at number 197 on the us billboard 200 chart.", "question": "what was the never story peaked at number on the us billboard 200 chart?", "answer": [197.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {"us": {"(1, 2)": "us"}, "peaked": {"(0, 2)": "peak chart positions"}, "200": {"(0, 2)": "peak chart positions"}}, "left": {"the never story": {"(2, 0)": "the never story"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(2, 2)": 197.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C5"], "reference_cells_map": {"C5": "(2, 2)"}}
{"id": "4ce90dd6def5be660ca951d19697b3a6", "table_id": "990", "table_source": "statcan", "sentence_id": "5709", "sub_sentence_id": "1", "sub_sentence": "acquittals were infrequent, representing 3% to 4% of decisions in adult criminal court cases over 2007/2008 and 2016/2017 and between 1% and 2% of decisions in youth court cases.", "question": "what were the percentages of adult acquitted in 2007/2008 and 2016/2017, and about youth respectively?", "answer": [3.0, 4.0, 1.0, 2.0], "aggregation": ["none"], "linked_cells": {"entity_link": {"top": {}, "left": {"acquittal": {"(4, 0)": "acquitted"}}, "top_left_corner": {}}, "quantity_link": {"[ANSWER]": {"(4, 2)": 3.0, "(4, 4)": 4.0, "(4, 6)": 1.0, "(4, 8)": 2.0}}}, "answer_formulas": ["=C7", "=E7", "=G7", "=I7"], "reference_cells_map": {"C7": "(4, 2)", "E7": "(4, 4)", "G7": "(4, 6)", "I7": "(4, 8)"}}
